<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Super VPN</string>
    <string name="vpn_on">VPN ON</string>
    <string name="vpn_off">VPN OFF</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">drawer open</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">drawer close</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="connecting">Connecting</string>
    <string name="disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="connection_close_confirm">Would you like to cancel the current VPN Connection?</string>
    <string name="yes">YES</string>
    <string name="no">NO</string>
    <string name="policydata">In Harry’s world fate works not only through powers and objects such as prophecies, the Sorting Hat, wands, and the Goblet of Fire, but also through people. Repeatedly, other characters decide Harry’s future for him, depriving him of freedom and choice. For example, before his eleventh birthday, the Dursleys control Harry’s life, keeping from him knowledge of his past and understanding of his identity (Sorcerer’s 49). In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Dobby repeatedly assumes control over events by intercepting Ron’s and Hermione’s letters during the summer; by sealing the barrier to Platform 93⁄4, causing Harry to miss the Hogwarts Express; and by sending a Bludger after Harry in a Quidditch match, breaking his wrist. Yet again, in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, many adults intercede while attempting to protect Harry from perceived danger, as Snape observes: “Everyone from the Minister of Magic downward has been trying to keep famous Harry Potter safe from Sirius Black” (284). All these characters, as enactors of fate, unknowingly drive Harry toward his destiny by attempting to control or to direct his life, while themselves controlled and directed by fate.
    In Harry’s world fate works not only through powers and objects such as prophecies, the Sorting Hat, wands, and the Goblet of Fire, but also through people. Repeatedly, other characters decide Harry’s future for him, depriving him of freedom and choice. For example, before his eleventh birthday, the Dursleys control Harry’s life, keeping from him knowledge of his past and understanding of his identity (Sorcerer’s 49). In Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets, Dobby repeatedly assumes control over events by intercepting Ron’s and Hermione’s letters during the summer; by sealing the barrier to Platform 93⁄4, causing Harry to miss the Hogwarts Express; and by sending a Bludger after Harry in a Quidditch match, breaking his wrist. Yet again, in Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban, many adults intercede while attempting to protect Harry from perceived danger, as Snape observes: “Everyone from the Minister of Magic downward has been trying to keep famous Har</string>
    <string name="agree">By tapping I agree, you agree to our</string>
    <string name="i_agree">I Agree</string>
    <string name="pref_previously_started">previouslyStarted</string>
    <string name="united_states">United States</string>
    string:
    <string name="Ad_AdAttribution">Ad</string>
    <string name="ADMOB_ADS_UNIT_ID">ca-app-pub-7294192697106684/3637019841</string>
    <!--    <string name="Fb_interstitial_id">194768635535878_194769225535819</string>-->
    <string name="Fb_interstitial_id">IMG_16_9_APP_INSTALL#YOUR_PLACEMENT_ID</string>
    <string name="fb_banner_id">IMG_16_9_APP_INSTALL#YOUR_PLACEMENT_ID</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_want_to_exit_this_app">Are you sure want to exit this app?</string>
    <string name="admob_interstitial_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/1033173712</string>
    <string name="admob_banner_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="select_server">Select Server</string>
    <string name="enjoying_supervpn">Enjoying SuperVPN</string>
    <string name="if_you_appreciate_it_please_give_up_5_star">If you appreciate it,please give up 5 star</string>
    <string name="nav_close">close</string>
    <string name="nav_open">OPen\n</string>
</resources>